[Music]
Hello friends, my name is Anil Rajpurohit,
and today I am presenting to you, on
this very day, August 8, 2013,
What Makes Non-Participants Show 11. Why are non-par
products so good? Because there is
zero investment risk in them,
because any return is guaranteed over a long period of time.
You get a regular income every year, and along with
this, you
also get income tax benefits. Because of the no-risk, regular
income, and tax benefits, non-par,
i.e., guaranteed plans, are so good and
so relevant.
So far, if we talk about ICC Prudential's
non-par products, their Gift and
Gift Long Term plans have sold very well,
and they are very good plans, they are quite good
in the market. Their sales are quite good right now.
And its already video,
which is about insurance, is already available on my YouTube channel,
Anil Rajpurohit.
If you want to see the Gift Long Term or
Gift Kar video in full detail,
then you can visit my YouTube channel and
I have also uploaded a screenshot of this
video for you.  You can see, let's
talk about what retirement benefits a customer gets,
most of all, will he get fixed income, will
he get increasing income, can
he get return of premium,
whatever premium he pays, can he get it
back, when can he get
return of premium back and the person taking
life insurance tax, whether he
wants to take more or less or not, then
these powers have been given to the customer in this policy, so
he can take fixed income, can take
increasing income, can take return
of premium, can take return of premium
whenever he wants, he can take insurance tax
even if he wants to take more or less,
now let's see what is there in it, you will see two options,
get level fixed income plus
return of premium is the first option,
you will get another option,
what is there in this, you decide your money back
amount from zero to 100%, in
what manner do you want the money back amount and
in which year do you want the money back amount, you
can decide here yourself, in which there is
level income
in this also  Decide your money back amount
You can select from zero
which gives 100% return.
Here you will see that you are being given the
option of premium payment from 5 years to 12
years. 5 to 12 5 6 7 8 9 10
11 12 You can pay premium for as many years as
you can afford to pay premium. Deferment
period is also given from 0 to 5 years.
After premium payment, if you
want to wait for more income, then you can
wait for 1 2 3 4 5 years. You can
take deferment period and for
how many years you want income, you can take yearly income as well as monthly income.
You have years to get income 5 7 10 12 15 20
25 30 Or you can take any year. If you want income for only 5 years,
you can also take it. If you
want income for 30 years, then also you can take this.  If
you take this policy then you will get 100% money
back and if you die during the income period then the
rest of the income will
come to you normally.
Now let us see an illustration of level income here, there is
a person
whose age is 40 years, he is buying a 2 year old Doberman
dog and he pays Rs 1 lakh each for 10
years, if
he purchases the policy on 1st August 2013, then he will pay the premium for 10 years
and
wait for 2 years, then from 2036, he will
start getting income from 1st August 2033, Rs 1 lakh 13 thousand
every year and this income will come for 30 years and
you will get Rs 10 lakh back
if you take 100% money back, that is, in the end, you
decide your money back amount,
now here you see that for how many years you are selecting it,
otherwise here you see the level income with other
percentage of income.  You see how much percentage of return of premium you
want to give,
but for example, you
get an option from zero to 100% here,
like
if you select here that I want
money at the end, I want level income at the end, then
in your example, it is
₹13490, but now
instead of 10 lakhs, you want to take only 50% of it, suppose
one ₹1 lakh for 10 years, you get 10 lakh rupees and another
10 lakhs back, you said no money back,
I have to select 50%, select 40%, select
10%, select 100%,
like if you select 50%, then at
maturity also you will get ₹5 lakhs
instead of 10 lakhs, but the income will be
₹17490 instead of 13 lakhs for 30 years, that is,
your income will increase by ₹4450 for the next 30 years,
so  Now you can decide here whether
you want 100% money or
50%, you want zero percent or 10%,
so whether you want more income in the beginning or
maturity, you can select this yourself.
Decide your money back or, like here
you will be given
an option as to
when you want money back, but on the exam, the customer
paid the premium for 10 years,
kept a development plan of two years, then only after 12 years,
if he paid
Rs. 10 lakh in 10 years, you will get the entire Rs. 10 lakh
here if you want, after that
your income will start coming continuously, so now
you can see here as an example
that if you had taken the income which
you saw in the beginning, it was ₹13490, but
if you had taken the on-mature i.e. premium
payment term and if you have taken any Daman trade
i.e. 10 years premium, 2 years wait, then
you want the money back only after 12 years.  If you
pay Rs 10 lakh, you will
get the full amount but then after that the
income that will come for 30 years will be Rs
33490. Right now how much is being paid, Rs 13490 and Rs 10 lakh is being
received later but here
you are getting Rs 10 lakh only for 12 years, then Rs 33490
income is being received.
Now let's see the option of increasing income
as you have seen here,
but here
your income will increase by 5% every year through simple interest, that is,
when the income starts, whatever
income you get in the first year, you will keep getting 5% of it every year through simple
interest. For example, there is
a customer on the exam whose age is
40 years, he is paying premium for 10 years and is
taking a development period of 2 years, he has paid Rs 1 lakh each
for 10 years and waited for 2 years, then
from August 2036,
he will start getting an income of Rs 77830
but at 5%  If there is an increase, it will be 81000 next year, in
this way it will keep increasing
and the income will keep increasing till the third year
and the 100% money that you had invested will
also be refunded to you, you
get 13490, the total income is 34 lakhs,
but if you have taken the option of increasing income,
that too the option of last income, then from the
first year onwards, you get
increasing income every year and the
total income you get is 4027000, you
get 623000 more income, it
is an increasing option,
as you saw in the beginning that if you want to take money back and
if you want to take 2 lakhs out of 10 lakhs or 5 lakhs, then the
income will be more and
decide your money back and
whenever the premium payment term is completed,
after that, if you want to withdraw money
again and again, 15 years, 20th year, 25 years,
after that you can take income, so the more
time you withdraw money later, the
more you will get.  Income will come. If you
need less income, you can withdraw money early if you
want.
Now you must have noticed that the income tax rules have
changed. In traditional policies, if you
pay a premium of Rs 5 lakh or more, then
your money gets waived by income tax.
But if you do not
want to pay a big amount as a customer, you
know that when your income comes after 10-12 years,
then the income tax slab becomes different, that too
technically. For example, at that time,
income of Rs 7 lakh or Rs 75 lakh
is tax free, I consider that up to Rs 15 lakh,
whatever income you are getting here, that too gets
technically taxed
for you. Or if you
can also take some income by reducing the insurance tax, I will
try to understand here a little bit
how the customer can avail this benefit.
For example,
here, if you
are 40 years old at the time, then Rs 10.65 means Rs 1 lakh.  There will be an
insurance tax of Rs 65,000 but if you do it,
which goes up to Rs 7 by selecting 7.5, that is,
against a premium of Rs 1 lakh, there will be Rs 7 lakh insurance, so
if your insurance is less than Rs 10 lakh,
technically the insurance gets reduced by 10 times, then anyway
your premium
income becomes taxable, even if you are
paying a premium of Rs 1 lakh, then
if technically you want more income
and it is still taxable, then
if you put in a bigger amount,
even Rs 10 lakh, then why don't you
decide on income that you have taken equal
insurance, then the income will be Rs
11,64,900, but if you take
insurance only once, then your income will
be Rs 11,85,900 instead of Rs 11,64, and
your income will increase by Rs 21,000, so if you
want to increase your income or if you are paying Rs 1 lakh
and you know that your income will
not exceed Rs 700,000  When your income starts
coming in, you must have retired and there will be
no income. So, if your income is
2 lakh or 2.5 lakh rupees in front of lakh rupees, then
it will be tax free anyway. So,
you can increase your income by taking this low insurance tax. There is
an option of SE D date in this.
How can you choose SE D date? If you want to
take money back of your policy on any special day like any festival season
or wedding anniversary or your birthday
or maturity of your policy, on any
such special occasion, if you want to take income every year, then
you can take it. But for example, Anil
Rajpurohit has purchased a policy on 1st
August 2013 but his birthday is on
12th October. When did he buy the policy? In August 2000, his
birthday is on 12th
October and he decided that
he should get income on 12th October every year. So,
now if he gets income in August, then he has got income
of Rs. 1013000.  It starts
from 1st August 203, but if he
starts getting it from 12th October 2035, then he will
start getting income a little early
and the income will be ₹16000 for the next 30 years. The
money deposited will be returned to him for ₹10 lakh.
So now this income will be given every year
on his birthday. There are
many unique features of the industry which are
not available in other insurance policies. This
policy is for the first time in the industry,
such as in which year you want the money back, if
you want to increase or decrease the amount of money back, if
you want to take increasing income, from the customer's
point of view, you want to take more income, then
these are unique features in the industry
which are available in this plan. Now, according to
your need, how
can you do the purchasing, that you thought
that I should get my money deposited back
and after that I will get 7% income on the money deposited,
but for example, your age is 40 years,
you have decided to pay the premium for 12 years
and for 3 years  If you give the document i.e.
waiting period, then the premium was paid for 12 years,
you waited for 3 years and then
your income will start coming from 2019, then
in 2038 you took the income of 12 lakhs,
after that
seven percent of 12 lakhs is 84000, it will keep
coming to you for the next 12 years,
take back the money taken and the total will remain equal to seven
percent, even after that you can take income,
secondly if you
pay the premium for 10 years, then you will get 10 lakhs back, even if you pay seven
percent of it, there will be no problem,
you will get an income of ₹1000 or ₹600 every year,
that will go on for the next 12 years, for this if you
want to take care of your child's education
when he turns 18 and
he needs more money for higher education, then
also you can take this policy
for child benefit, that is, pay the
premium for 12 years, keep a development plan of 5 years for the
child.  There is zero ahead and the
father's age is 35 years ahead, the
child will be 18 years old, the father will be 53 years old
then he needs income, at 18 years the
income will be 22000, then 2 lakh 33000, then 2
lakh 44000 and in this way the
income will increase to even two lakhs which will be less for higher education
and in 12 years
you will get your 12 lakh rupees back
tax free.
Now if you want retirement point of
Vijay, say you are 40 years old, you
will retire around 5860, then you
need money that too tax free, so say you pay one
lakh rupees each for your 12 years, you have taken the deferment of five years,
so now whatever
money you increase here,
you will get back 5.6 times of that total, 10 lakh 12,
so you will get 56 lakhs back, but in what
manner will the income come every year, at 58 ₹195, then
25000 this every year  It will grow at 5% simple interest
and your income will reach ₹418000
whereas today you will be 87, the
income will keep coming till then, suppose you die after the age of 75, the
rest of the income that is withdrawn will
come to you normally but it will come 100% guaranteed,
tax will come, now if you
want to get six times your income return, suppose you
pay Rs 1 lakh each for 10 years
and you decide to take income for 30 years,
how many 30 years, then first pay Rs 97000, in
this way the amount will grow to 37000
and the money saved will be returned to ₹10 lakh,
now if you want you
can pay 12 premiums, then pay a
premium of ₹10 lakh for 10 years and you
give development for 2 years, this is your 40 years,
then you will get a head of approximately 7% and the return increases,
error text three with
insurance tax of 6.83 with this tax benefit
So how much income will you get every year?
In the first year you got eight lakh
one thousand, in 2036 you got ₹850000, then you got ₹
810000, this will keep increasing and will reach
1990 thousand and you will get your ₹1
crore back tax free, so
this is also yours, if you are not such a customer who
wants to take the benefit, you
can take the top up of this type of policy,
what will be there in the policy that you
want to avail, this policy also has the benefit of loan, there is a
revival period of 5 years in this policy, or
if you are not able to pay the premium due to any tax, then
you can revive the policy by paying the late fee for the number of years which is pending,
you will get a grace period of 30 days, if you pay your
premium, if you purchase your policy on 8th
August 2013, then next year
your premium will be due on 8th August 2024, you will have a
grace period of one month, so if
you pay the premium till 8th September, then you
can pay it brother,  If the minister is in a good mood,
you will get a grace period of 15 days and
you will also get a free look print of 15 days.
If you want to cancel the policy, you
can cancel it within 15 days
and you will also get the tax benefit of ATC
and you will get tax free benefit of 10-10 days. If the
investment is up to Rs 5 lakh and
above Rs 5 lakh, then there will be no benefit of 10-20 days. So,
you
can purchase this plan as per your need. If you
liked my video, you can subscribe to my YouTube channel
and my mobile
number is also mentioned here. Thank
you. So it is a match.
Now let us understand,
try to understand its illustration in short, which
I explained to you in the beginning. The name of the ICC Pro
Gift Pro
propose is Anil Rajpurohit and
I have taken the illustration for 40 years ahead.
Here we are packing a premium of Rs 1 lakh for
10 years.  And they purchase the policy on 8th August 2023
when the policy product has been
launched today and till 8th August 2032 they
will pay the premium for 10 years only,
they decide to take income for 30 years
and also want their money back, whoever
is a fan of India, then their income will
start coming from 2003 and
this policy will run till 8th August 2065, here they will get a
nominal income of Rs.
13490, income will start for the next 30 years from
8th August 2032 to 2065, they will get Rs.
10 lakh in 10 years, when will they
get it, Rs. 10000,
life insurance
tax at 65, the premium will remain yours
for 10 years, otherwise you have
decided the premium amount to be Rs. 1 lakh, if we
talk about ICC Prudential, till now
7 crore 72 lakh people have purchased the policy,
if by 30th May 2023, the amount of Rs.
2.36 lakh crore will be  The company has given benefits till now,
like bonus etc. By combining all this, it is a
company worth 2.5 lakh crores. This is the value of assets and
management or the valuation of the company. So, the
value of this company is 2.5
lakh crores. It settles claims within 24 hours.
If you have provided all the documents on time,
you will also get tax benefits. You can keep
them.
And from here, let us understand how it works. You are
paying premium for 12 years. The
policy term is 12 years, that is, there is a
development period of 2 years. You take that premium pack of ₹1 lakh. The
name of the pack is ICC
Proof Gift Pro and here he is
not taking tax on the option, that is, he is
not taking 7 times insurance tax, he is taking minimum 10
times. Which insurance option is he selecting from the first day? He is
taking the option of level guaranteed income.
He has not taken the option of SEBI date and there was a
hundred percent money back, but
in which year should it start from 42, that is, in the
policy  I want
113490 income, take that name of the bastard, there are six of them,
their annual income is 1 lakh 13490, for how many
years will the income come for 30 years and
how much money will I get, 10 lakh rupees.
Now here, look at the table in this way, pay
one lakh rupees each for 10 years,
from the first day you take insurance, you will keep taking
insurance till the term of your policy is there,
then you will start getting guaranteed benefit every year in the form of survival benefit of
1 lakh
13490 for 30 years and if I am in India,
you will get 10 lakh rupees back, so
now this is the earlier option, I had explained in great detail so that
you
understand everything quickly and if here, suppose the
customer dies at the age of 15 or 16, then the
remaining income will go to the
nominee, now if you see the option number,
if you see later, then you will
see here that
you have selected level guaranteed
income here and here you have
money back  You want to take hundred percent
but when do you want to take the money? You
want to take it in the 27th year or in the 42nd year, if not then
how much income will you get? For how many
years will the income come? It is
not necessary for 10 years, you
can take income for 30 years, at most, for
10 years and after that, for 10 years, income of ₹ 2 lakh 39410 was given
and you got back the money of 12 lakh, right? For
30 years, you need 12 years,
income was given and you got back the money of 12 lakh, in
this way, you have selected for how many years you
want income. Now
see the option here, you have again given the option of level income
and here the
monthly money back, which I am
not taking in full, I am taking only 50%, so
what happened to your income, here instead of 13, there was an
income of 17 and here the 10 lakhs which were to be
returned, 5 lakhs came back.
If you look at the next option, then what did you do here, you
got level guaranteed income but
When are you withdrawing the money? You are
withdrawing it in the 12th year itself. You are withdrawing the money after some time of studying
that brother, I
paid Rs 10 lakh in 10 years for a waiting period of two years,
after that I got
back the entire amount I paid, even after that my
income of Rs 33490 will keep coming for the next 30 years.
What is the next option that you have
selected here, how much will the increasing income
increase, 5% with simple interest, so now from
here you will see that it is
increasing by 5% every year and the
money is invested and you get a refund.
Next, if you see the option,
here you have taken income for 30 years
and that too level income, but here it is
not like this, if you are investing Rs 10 lakh as a customer,
because
if you
see the insurance tax here, then you have selected option four low tax here, that is,
your insurance
tax will be 7 times, so this income will be taxable to you,
but you will get more income of Rs 11
lakh.  You will get an income of Rs 85900 and later
you will get a refund of Rs 1 crore. In the same
way, you can fill the last form. If I
tell you, then here you will notice that
you have
decided to withdraw the money in the 15th year
and have decided to withdraw 100% of the money. So,
here you see, you got
back Rs 12 lakh in 12 years and
for the next 12 years you got an income of Rs 84 thousand, that is,
you are getting 7% income of the deposited money every year. So, according to
your need,
you can do any of these policies by selecting the option based on your need.
So, if you
finally review this, this plan
is also an excellent plan. You
must see, whether it is your child's education or your
own retirement, you need guaranteed returns, you
need short term income, long term income,
early income, later income. So,
all the options are given to you. The
option of SEBI date is given. It is
tax benefit, it is not good. By
taking unit features for the customer  If you have come, then this
is a product with great features and
you can definitely purchase it according to your need, be it short term or long term,
so if
you liked this entire video of mine, then before leaving,
please subscribe to my channel Anil Rajbhar
and if possible,
like and share this video, thank you so much.